downloadwap.com 2019-05-12

# PHONEKY -

### Privacy Policy

**Security**  
PHONEKY takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

**Information Collection and Use**  
PHONEKY is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties.

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties.

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware PHONEKY is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Because your privacy is important to us and to better protect it, we provide the following notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**Summary**

This Privacy Policy of PHONEKY, outlines how your personally identifiable information (PII) and other personal data (your "user information") will be collected, used, and shared in connection with your access to and/or use of phoneky.com (the "Site"), and any newsletters, content, features, services, or other offerings that PHONEKY may provide in connection therewith.

This Privacy Policy also describes your choices and rights regarding the use, access and correction or deletion of your user information. By using the Site, you consent to the use of your user information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you are located in the EU, you will also be asked to provide clear and unequivocal affirmative consent to the collection, processing, and sharing of your user information via cookies and similar technologies. The Site is owned and operated by PHONEKY.

Notice to EU Individuals: this Privacy Policy and its enumerated policies are intended to comply with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 (the "General Data Protection Regulation" or "GDPR") and provide appropriate protection and care with respect to the treatment of your user information in accordance with the GDPR.

**Information Collection and Use**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Site as well as related third-party websites.

We do not send any e-mail notifications except the password reminder and signup confirmation emails..

**Third Party Sites**

Our Sites may link to other websites that are not under our control. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from our Sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and PHONEKY is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that is written to your computer's hard drive by your web browser. A cookie file can contain and/or automatically collect information, such as a user identification code or IP address, that a website will use to track the pages and number of times you have visited. The data read from these cookies may be linked to personally identifying (PII) and non-personally identifying (non-PII) information.

We and the third-party companies we employ use cookies and similar technologies on the Sites to personalize and optimize your browsing experience and the Sites by:

providing you tailored ads and content,  
enabling social media features,  
safeguarding against spam and malware,  
analyzing trends, traffic, and user behavior,  
administering the website,  
gathering demographic data about our user base as a whole,  
tracking web and advertising analytics throughout the Sites  
performing location-related functionalities and analytics, and  
educating ourselves about how we can continue to improve the Sites and its various elements.  
If you would like more information about the above practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by our partner companies, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative's tool for opting out of interest-based advertising.

**Google Adsense**

We use third-party advertising companies to collect information by placing advertising cookies provided by Google Adsense on your computer when you visit our Sites. These advertising cookies are used for the purpose of personalization to target ads specifically based on your interests. For details on the data that Google Adsense collects and how to exercise your options with the network, please visit and read Google Adsense's Privacy Policy.

**Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics to collect website analytics about our users. Website analytics refers to a set of tools used to collect and analyze anonymous usage information, enabling us to better understand how our Sites are used. This, in turn, enables us to improve our Sites and the services offered through it. For more specific details on how Google collects and uses data when you use our Sites, please visit and read Google's Privacy Policy.

**Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn**

We use cookies from social media companies to determine certain actions taken by users who visit our Sites. For more specific details on each of these companies, please visit and read Facebook's Cookies Policy, Twitter's Cookies Policy, and LinkedIn's Cookie Policy.

**In the Event of Sale or Bankruptcy**

The ownership of the Sites may change at some point in the future. Should that occur, we want our Site to be able to maintain a relationship with you. In the event of a sale, merger, public offering, bankruptcy or other change in control of PHONEKY, your information may be shared with the person or business that owns or controls this site. Opting out of receiving information from third parties will not affect our right to transfer your information to a new owner, but your choices will continue to be respected regarding the use of your information. You will be notified as described below in "Changes to this Privacy Policy."

**As Required By Law**

PHONEKY may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law such as to comply with a subpoena or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on PHONEKY or to protect and defend the rights or property of PHONEKY.

Notice to EU Individuals: As outlined in this Privacy Statement, PHONEKY will not process your user information without a lawful basis to do so, as such bases are defined in Article 6 of the GDPR. In general, PHONEKY will process your user information on the legal bases of consent, contract (if you have entered into an agreement with us and such processing is a necessary part thereof), or legal obligation (as noted above). PHONEKY may also process certain user information on the basis of the following legitimate interests, provided that such interests are not overridden by your privacy rights and interests: delivering and continuing to develop and improve the Site, learning from your behavior on the Site (e.g., analyzing traffic) to better serve you and other Site users, helping us modify or enhance the Site and its content, receiving insight as to what users do (and don't) like about our Site or aspects thereof, and providing a stable, consistent, and secure user experience in connection with the Site.

**Data Security**

We care about the protection of your user information and attempt to follow accepted industry standards to protect personal information you have provided. However, no method of data transmission or electronic storage on the Internet is guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.

**Privacy of Children**

The Site is intended for people who are at least 18 years of age. If you are less than 18 years old, please do not send any user information to us--including information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. We do not knowingly collect (nor do we wish to collect) any personally identifiable information or other user information from children under the age of 18. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 18, we will delete that information from our database and terminate the corresponding account, if any. We encourage you to discuss the Site with your parent or guardian.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or how to remove or modify your user information or related consents, please feel free to contact us at info  phoneky.com

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

PHONEKY reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, at any time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time such information is used.

Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page. If we make a material change to our privacy practices, we will provide notice on the site or by other means as appropriate.

**Last Updated:** November 01, 2018
